<help>
Welcome to Królewska Piaskownica server!
This server is currently in early stage, if you encounter any bugs, please inform a higher authority on the server.

   *** Below you will find all the necessary informations to get you started! ***

   Last update 22.02.17


   1. Joining a lobby
      Joining a lobby is simple. Upon pressing F2, a room window will appear (F2 again to close it). It contains all the necessary informations on the room.
         Name - Room's name
         Players - How many players are playing/joined the queue (players/maxplayers)
         Status - "waiting" or "starting" signals that the room is open for joining. However if the room is "started" nobody can join it.
      After selecting a desired room, simply pressing button "Join" on the right from the list.
      If there are 2 or more people in the room, the game will start after 30 seconds (for the time it gets status "started")
 
   2. Basic rules and gameplay
      2.1. Match procedures
         a. Upon a match start, every player is spawned above Los Santos with parachutes (will also be pushed in a random angle from there).
         b. There are 180 seconds until the green (safe) zone appears in random location and toxic gasses start narrowing the playable area.
         c. In the meantime players should look for weapons, medications, other items and vehicles placed around LS to get prepared for encounters.
         d. The last person to survive wins the match and is sent to lobby.
      
      2.2. Using items
         a. After walking over a pickupable item, there will be a message shown in the middle of the screen with name of the item.
         b. To pick up an item, "X" key is used.
         c. To use an item, "H" key is pressed. Player will be shown with inventory window, double-clicking (lmb) an item will use that item. If it's weapon it will equip it.
 
   3. Features to be done.
      We plan many more features than there already is. Some of them are:
         - deathmatch rooms and more gamemodes,
         - custom skins and custom CJ clothes,
         - global ranks and reward system,
         - excluded weapons and ammo,
         - options and bindable hotkeys,
         - advanced analyzed statistics,
         - account levels,
         - stacked items,
         - spawn lobby
 
   We hope to see you collaborate with us in developing this server!
 
   4. Disclaimer      
      Królewska Piaskownica Battle Royale gamemode is made and owned by PK "Yazir".
      If you see any other server using near exact same gamemode, please report that to respective owner.

      KP uses few open source resources which can be found on mtasa-resources.

KP©2017
</help>